(Sheldon:)Are you two ever getting married?
(Sheldon:)And, if so, where will we all live?
Have you thought about that?
(Leonard:)-No.
-Penny?
OK, wait. What are we doing?
(Leonard:)For some reason,
we're planning a future
(Leonard:)where we both live
with Sheldon forever.
(Sheldon:)Good. Now we're getting somewhere.
(Penny:)Look, I know you think I'm being
reckless, and you might be right,
(Penny:)but I need to take this shot.
(Sheldon:)No kidding. Despite what it says
on her resume, she is no longer 22.
(Leonard:)I swear, I am on your side.
(Penny:)You keep saying you're on my
side, but you don't act like it.
(Sheldon:)He does that to me, too.
Why do we put up with it?
(Leonard:)Listen, I could never do
what you're doing, okay?
(Leonard:)-I would be terrified.
-Well, it's scary for me, too.
(Sheldon:)I'm fine with it.
(Leonard:)My point is, just because I couldn't
do it doesn't mean you shouldn't.
(Leonard:)And I'm proud of you.
(Penny:)Okay. Thank you.